<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<resources>
    <!-- Play Store specific strings -->

    <!-- Translators: 30 character limit -->
    <string name="market_title">Metrodroid (was Farebot M)</string>

    <!-- Translators: 80 character limit -->
    <string name="market_short_desc">Metrodroid can read information from some public transport NFC smartcards.</string>

    <!-- Translators: 4000 character limit -->
    <string name="market_long_desc">Metrodroid can read information from some public transport NFC smartcards. It was formerly known as Farebot M.\n\nThis is a fork of Eric Butler\\\'s Farebot project, with support for additional cards and bug fixes.\n\nSupported cards:\n- Bilhete Único - São Paulo, Brazil [1] [2] [5]\n- Clipper - San Francisco, CA, USA\n- EZ-Link - Singapore [3]\n- Go card - Brisbane and South East Queensland, Australia [0] [1] [2]\n- Manly Fast Ferry - Sydney, NSW, Australia [0] [1] [2]\n- Matkakortti, HSL - Finland\n- Myki - Melbourne (and surrounds), VIC, Australia [0] [4]\n- MyWay - Australian Capital Territory, Australia [0] [1] [2] [5]\n- NETS Flashpay - Singapore\n- Octopus - Hong Kong [0]\n- Opal - Sydney (and surrounds), NSW, Australia [0]\n- ORCA - Seattle, WA, USA\n- OV-chipkaart - Netherlands [1] [2]\n- Shenzhen Tong - Shenzong, Guangdong Province, China [0]\n- Suica, IOCOA, PASMO, Edy - Japan\n- Transit Access Pass - Los Angeles, CA, USA [0] [1] [2]\n\n[0]: New in Metrodroid.\n[1]: Not compatible with all devices (Mifare Classic).\n[2]: Encryption keys are required to read this card.\n[3]: Not compatible with all devices (CEPAS).\n[4]: Only the card number can be read.\n[5]: Fallback reader -- must be explicitly enabled in the application\\\'s preferences.\n\nYou require a NFC-compatible phone in order to read cards.\n\nYou need a NXP NFC chipset in your phone in order to read MIFARE Classic cards.  Some phones have NFC chips from other manufacturers, which do not read Mifare Classic cards (eg: Nexus 4, Nexus 5, Samsung Galaxy S4). Check the About screen in the app in order to determine if your phone supports MIFARE Classic.\n\nSome agencies have encrypted cards. You will need to acquire encryption keys in order to read them. These are generally unique to each card. Sorry, I can\\\'t help you with this.\n\nSome other agencies\\\' cards using Cubic Nextfare on Mifare Classic may also work.\n\nFor more details about permissions required, please see the privacy policy.\n\nThis software is licensed under the GNU GPLv3+, source code is available at https://github.com/micolous/metrodroid/</string>

    <!-- Translators: 500 character limit -->
    <string name="market_changelog_30">* Multiple fixes for Cubic Nextfare cards.\n* Fudan FM11RF08 cards are no longer falsely detected as Bilhete Único.\n* Adds experimental support for MyWay (ACT, Australia).\n* Works around Mifare Classic bugs on some HTC and Sony devices.\n* Fix permissions bugs on Android 6 and later.\n\nMore details: https://github.com/micolous/metrodroid/wiki/Changelog</string>

    <!-- Translators: 500 character limit -->
    <string name="market_changelog_29">* Improve reliability authenticating with Mifare Classic cards.\n* Adds support for Octopus (Hong Kong), Shenzhen Tong and Transit Access Pass (Los Angeles, CA, US).\n* Adds a generic reader for Cubic Nextfare MFC (based on Go card reader).\n* Export to USB Storage now allows you to pick a location on Android 4.4 (KitKat) and later.\n* Go card: Fares are now retrieved from the card, so should work with all stations. Added 7 extra stations. Now detects Adult and Concession cards.</string>

    <!-- Translators: 500 character limit -->
    <string name="market_changelog_28">* Now requires Android 4.1, to fix a map issue.\n* Added support for viewing raw FeliCa data.\n* Added support for Mifare Ultralight, including raw data.\n* Fixed an issue where 2 trips on different days may not show the date header on the earlier trip (Issue #15).\n* Go card: Added 11 extra stops, thanks to data donations. Implement fare calculation, with some limitations.\n\nMore details: https://github.com/micolous/metrodroid/wiki/Changelog</string>

    <!-- Translators: 500 character limit -->
    <string name="market_changelog_27">Farebot M is now Metrodroid.\n\n* Implemented support for reading the card number from Myki (VIC, AU).\n* Last digit of Go Card (Brisbane, AU) is now read.\n* Improved handling of Mifare DESFire cards.\n* Fixed support for NETS Flashpay (Singapore) cards which are also credit cards (patch by @chrisplus).\n* Japanese translation improved greatly (thanks to @naofum).\n* Trips and Refills are now combined into \"History\" for all cards.\n\nMore details: https://github.com/micolous/metrodroid/wiki/Changelog</string>

    <!-- Translators: 500 character limit -->
    <string name="market_changelog_26">Happy new year!\n\n* Added basic support for Go card (Brisbane and South East Queensland, AU). Requires encryption keys (which are unique to each card) and device with Mifare Classic support. Limited stop support.\n* Added card identification support for Adelaide Metrocard, AT HOP and Myki.\n* Fixed importing individual cards from XML files.\n* Various UI improvements.\n* Minor bug fixes.\n\nMore details: https://github.com/micolous/metrodroid/wiki/Changelog</string>

</resources>
